A Guide to the Governor Henry Lee Executive Papers, 1791-1794
Library of Virginia
- Oversized (Newspaper Box)
  - 1793
    - Jan. 1 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Feb. 4 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - March 12 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - July 21 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Sept. 5 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Sept. [N.D.] (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Dec. 13 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - 1794
    - Jan. 31 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - March 15 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - June 2 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Point of Fork Arsenal - Returns, 1792-1794 (Box 10, Folder 24)